{
    "subject": "resource/Phillip_Johnston",
    "predicate": "property/associatedActs",
    "object": "Transparent Quartet",
    "human_readable": "Phillip Johnston is associated with the band Transparent Quartet.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9227215051651001,
            "question": "Who is associated with the band Transparent Quartet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8455400466918945,
            "question": "Name a band that Phillip Johnston is part of."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7838920950889587,
            "question": "Is Phillip Johnston a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7765387296676636,
            "question": "What band is Phillip Johnston known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7213457822799683,
            "question": "With what musical group is Phillip Johnston connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6060685515403748,
            "question": "What kind of music does Transparent Quartet play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5542405843734741,
            "question": "When was Transparent Quartet formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.514773428440094,
            "question": "Where is Transparent Quartet based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4631505012512207,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs by Transparent Quartet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32815784215927124,
            "question": "Has Transparent Quartet won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Phillip Johnston is associated with the band Transparent Quartet.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4317_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous songs by Transparent Quartet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4317_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Transparent Quartet based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4317_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Transparent Quartet formed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4317_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4317_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Phillip Johnston being associated with the Transparent Quartet, including his role as a leader and composer for the group."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Phillip Johnston is associated with the band Transparent Quartet.\" This is evident from the following excerpts:\n\n- From file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4317/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt`: \"Presenting his new drum-less band The Transparent Quartet, Johnston aims to combine the discipline and dynamics of a chamber music group with the energy and freedom of a jazz combo.\"\n- From file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4317/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt`: \"Phillip Johnston Transparent Quartet\" and further details about the band's repertoire and members.\n- From file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4317/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt`: \"The Transparent Quartet began around 1995. This four-piece group combined influences ranging from European classical music, twentieth-century composition, the West Coast \u201ccool school,\u201d and experimental jazz.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}